
=== waiting period for pre-existing diseases
0.746  Kotak General ù Health Car   p5    In the event that any of the above Illnesses/conditions are Pre-existing Diseases at the Policy
0.703  Kotak General ù Health Car   p4    All waiting periods will apply individually to each Insured Person: 3.1 Pre-Existing Disease Wa
0.676  United India ù Group Healt   p10   iii. If any of the specified disease/procedure falls under the waiting period specified for pre
0.658  Kotak General ù Health Car   p7    In case policies accepted with loadings, waiting period for Pre-existing disease's as well as 2
0.642  SBI General ù SuperHealth    p46   Waiting period specific to these ailments are mentioned in E. IV and V. II) Specified diseases 

=== cashless hospitalisation process
0.683  HDFC ERGO ù Optima Restore   p8    f. Cashless Service: Treatment, Consultation or Procedure Treatment, Consultation or Procedure 
0.678  Care Health ù Group Health   p31   Date and place of Injury or Death and/or Date of admission to Hospital or proposed date of admi
0.667  HDFC ERGO ù Optima Restore   p8    v) Cashless service: If any treatment, consultation or procedure for which a claim may be made 
0.628  Future Generali ù Group He   p9    Cashless treatment is only available at a Network Provider. In order to avail of cashless treat
0.621  Kotak General ù Health Car   p6    5. CLAIMS PROCEDURE On the occurrence or discovery of any Illness or Injury that may give rise 

=== maternity coverage exclusions
0.774  Care Health ù Group Health   p20   4.2. Specific Exclusions: 1. Waiting Period: Maternity wait period (applicable only for Benefit
0.744  Future Generali ù Group He   p24   2. EXTENSION FOR MATERNITY AND CHILD COVER This is an optional cover which can be obtained on p
0.741  United India ù Group Healt   p8    OPTIONAL COVER 4.6 Maternity Expenses Cover (Within Base Sum Insured): We will cover Medical Ex
0.739  United India ù Group Healt   p9    Note: When Maternity Expenses Cover has been opted for, the exclusion No.5.9 of the policy stan
0.711  Care Health ù Group Health   p12   vi. Congenital Diseases (internal & external) of new born child is covered under this Benefit. 

=== room rent sub-limit
0.522  Future Generali ù Health S   p7    For Topaz and Ruby Plans, in case You or insured person opts for a room with rent higher than t
0.515  Future Generali ù Group He   p23   Special conditions applicable to Extension for Room rent i. Copayment on Associated Medical exp
0.486  Kotak General ù Health Car   p14   Under this optional extension the insured is entitled for a discount in base premium as entitle
0.485  Aditya Birla ù Group Activ   p44   62. Renewal means the terms on which the contract of insurance can be renewed on mutual consent
0.484  Future Generali ù Health S   p6    52. Room Rent means the amount charged by a Hospital towards Room and B oarding expenses and sh
