
====================================================================================================
QUERY: waiting period for pre-existing diseases
====================================================================================================

-- vector only --
  1. [0.746] Kotak General ù Health C   p5    In the event that any of the above Illnesses/conditions are Pre-existi
  2. [0.703] Kotak General ù Health C   p4    All waiting periods will apply individually to each Insured Person: 3.
  3. [0.676] United India ù Group Hea   p10   iii. If any of the specified disease/procedure falls under the waiting
  4. [0.658] Kotak General ù Health C   p7    In case policies accepted with loadings, waiting period for Pre-existi
  5. [0.642] SBI General ù SuperHealt   p46   Waiting period specific to these ailments are mentioned in E. IV and V

-- after reranking --
  1. [+9.04] ( was #4) Kotak General ù Health C   p7    In case policies accepted with loadings, waiting period for Pre-existi
  2. [+8.40] ( was #2) Kotak General ù Health C   p4    All waiting periods will apply individually to each Insured Person: 3.
  3. [+7.86] ( was #3) United India ù Group Hea   p10   iii. If any of the specified disease/procedure falls under the waiting
  4. [+7.73] (was #16) Future Generali ù Health   p19   2 years and 3 years policy terms Available Available Available Availab  <-- promoted
  5. [+7.23] ( was #6) Future Generali ù Health   p9    Future Health Suraksha | Policy Wordings Page | 9 C. EXCLUSIONS 1. Wai  <-- promoted

====================================================================================================
QUERY: cashless hospitalisation process
====================================================================================================

-- vector only --
  1. [0.683] HDFC ERGO ù Optima Resto   p8    f. Cashless Service: Treatment, Consultation or Procedure Treatment, C
  2. [0.678] Care Health ù Group Heal   p31   Date and place of Injury or Death and/or Date of admission to Hospital
  3. [0.667] HDFC ERGO ù Optima Resto   p8    v) Cashless service: If any treatment, consultation or procedure for w
  4. [0.628] Future Generali ù Group    p9    Cashless treatment is only available at a Network Provider. In order t
  5. [0.621] Kotak General ù Health C   p6    5. CLAIMS PROCEDURE On the occurrence or discovery of any Illness or I

-- after reranking --
  1. [+6.12] ( was #6) Aditya Birla ù Group Act   p22   c. Process to be followed for Availing Cashless Facilities in Emergenc  <-- promoted
  2. [+5.05] ( was #5) Kotak General ù Health C   p6    5. CLAIMS PROCEDURE On the occurrence or discovery of any Illness or I
  3. [+4.57] ( was #4) Future Generali ù Group    p9    Cashless treatment is only available at a Network Provider. In order t
  4. [+4.40] ( was #3) HDFC ERGO ù Optima Resto   p8    v) Cashless service: If any treatment, consultation or procedure for w
  5. [+4.37] ( was #1) HDFC ERGO ù Optima Resto   p8    f. Cashless Service: Treatment, Consultation or Procedure Treatment, C

====================================================================================================
QUERY: maternity coverage exclusions
====================================================================================================

-- vector only --
  1. [0.774] Care Health ù Group Heal   p20   4.2. Specific Exclusions: 1. Waiting Period: Maternity wait period (ap
  2. [0.744] Future Generali ù Group    p24   2. EXTENSION FOR MATERNITY AND CHILD COVER This is an optional cover w
  3. [0.741] United India ù Group Hea   p8    OPTIONAL COVER 4.6 Maternity Expenses Cover (Within Base Sum Insured):
  4. [0.739] United India ù Group Hea   p9    Note: When Maternity Expenses Cover has been opted for, the exclusion 
  5. [0.711] Care Health ù Group Heal   p12   vi. Congenital Diseases (internal & external) of new born child is cov

-- after reranking --
  1. [+5.58] ( was #1) Care Health ù Group Heal   p20   4.2. Specific Exclusions: 1. Waiting Period: Maternity wait period (ap
  2. [+5.38] ( was #4) United India ù Group Hea   p9    Note: When Maternity Expenses Cover has been opted for, the exclusion 
  3. [+4.41] ( was #2) Future Generali ù Group    p24   2. EXTENSION FOR MATERNITY AND CHILD COVER This is an optional cover w
  4. [+3.32] (was #12) SBI General ù SuperHealt   p47   V) Medical Treatment Abroad: Expenses related to the treatment taken a  <-- promoted
  5. [+2.68] ( was #5) Care Health ù Group Heal   p12   vi. Congenital Diseases (internal & external) of new born child is cov

====================================================================================================
QUERY: room rent sub-limit
====================================================================================================

-- vector only --
  1. [0.522] Future Generali ù Health   p7    For Topaz and Ruby Plans, in case You or insured person opts for a roo
  2. [0.515] Future Generali ù Group    p23   Special conditions applicable to Extension for Room rent i. Copayment 
  3. [0.486] Kotak General ù Health C   p14   Under this optional extension the insured is entitled for a discount i
  4. [0.485] Aditya Birla ù Group Act   p44   62. Renewal means the terms on which the contract of insurance can be 
  5. [0.484] Future Generali ù Health   p6    52. Room Rent means the amount charged by a Hospital towards Room and 

-- after reranking --
  1. [+3.88] (was #13) Future Generali ù Health   p2    the following limits s hall apply in case of a claim o Room Board & Nu  <-- promoted
  2. [+2.60] (was #12) Care Health ù Group Heal   p17   3.11. Optional Benefit 7: Room Rent Modification Notwithstanding anyth  <-- promoted
  3. [+1.85] (was #10) Future Generali ù Group    p23   Annexure II: OPTIONAL COVERS 1. EXTENSION FOR ROOM RENT This is an opt  <-- promoted
  4. [+1.26] (was #15) Future Generali ù Health   p7    medical devices and diagnostics) Applicable for Topaz and Ruby Plans C  <-- promoted
  5. [+0.98] ( was #2) Future Generali ù Group    p23   Special conditions applicable to Extension for Room rent i. Copayment 
